Nathan Bright

Technical Support Specialist - University Medical Center

College Station, TX 77845 nathanbright@outlook.com 806-535-6587

Educated in CompTIA training courses during high-school curriculum, worked in IT industry since 2013. Planned education in business and pursuit of training in multiple fields of Information Technology and business management to better understand and present the proper solution to any global company need.

Work Experience

Technical Support Specialist

University Medical Center May 2015 to Present

Supported hospital-wide end users in IT Help Desk related issues

Active Directory end user group management

Troubleshot Cerner, Citrix, Imprivata, GE Centricity, GPMS software systems

Maintained business devices desktops/laptops/mobiles/printers/medical networking devices

IT Technician

Systek Computing - College Station, TX May 2014 to 2015

Software Repair & Sales May 2014-2015

Systek Computing

Hardware repair on desktop/laptop/mobile/server systems

Full service virus cleaning, computer optimization and backup setup

Troubleshooting of Windows OS (XP- Server 2012) and Mac OSX (Yosemite)

Direct businesss contact about sales, scheduling, repair, and other services provided by company

IT Contractor

Scott & White Healthcare - College Station, TX May 2013 to August 2013

Deployment of all devices ranging from company phones, computers, tablets, to advanced network health equipment

Imaging of upwards of 1000+ computers

Supervision of IT Contracting group of 5+ members

Inventory Management of large-scale infrastructure equipment

Label/Basic/Bracelet Printers installed on network.

Education

IT Administration

BLINN University - Bryan, TX 2017 to Present

Certified in IT

A&M Consolidated High-school - College Station, TX 2009 to 2013

Skills

TRAINING

Additional Information

Operating Systems
Training In windows system from XP to Win10
Max OSX
Cerner Software